Seino! Hello! I'm Shachi!
I'm Nao!
I'm Hanaka!
Today, I was in Gero for a location shoot.
But Hou and I had some free time, so we came to Takayama!
We came to Takayama!
Yay! We're here!
Well, we're off duty.
Yes, we are off today.
Yes, that's why we came to Takayama.
Takayama is a drama called Ijiua Gift,
Ijiua Gift, a drama by Mater.
It's a drama by Mater, and it aired in 2018.
Its theme song was Dreamer
That's right, Dreamer!
Yes, it's been a while since I've been here.
Yeah? We had a small part in it.
I haven't been here since that shoot. I'm Takayama.
Really?
Yeah.
Have fun. We'll just have fun.
Yeah, the city is just great.
Well, I'm hungry. Let's eat. I'd like to walk.
Let's go! Then we'll walk and look for lunch.
It's spring! Haru?
You know, from Nobunaga's Ambition.
Spring! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I want meat! I want some Hida beef!
Want some meat?
Hey...
But we're kind of on a foodie kick. Sushi? Meat sushi?
Yes! They have meat sushi!
You said you had that, so let's have it.
Let's eat.
Oh! That's it! That one!
But you're sure it's not open today?
It's definitely not open.
I heard they're closed a lot today.
They're closed on Tuesdays.
Oh, you okay?
Let's go down the street. Let's go down this street.
There's a lot of stuff here.
Okay.
Cute.
Oh! It's a camon!
I want you to make me a camon.
I'll make it myself.
I'll make a handmade camomile.
Wow! That's amazing!
I heard it takes three weeks.
But... But wouldn't it be so cool to have it in the house?
But, you know, we all have one of those.
Yes, yes, yes.
I want a camon!
My dad showed me something.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
He made it for me.
Yubamaki, yubamaki.
I like yuba.
No, I don't! I'm not doing it! I didn't do it!
Today, we can all take a break.
Yes, we do.
Hirahiu curry!
Looks delicious.
Are you doing it?
Isn't the curry good?
Let's see.
Oh, English!
Ingredients on the left.
We're closed on Tuesdays.
No, it's not.
What's wrong with everyone, Tuesday?
On the contrary.
If we sell on Tuesdays, we'll sell a lot.
I wonder if there are any stores that do Tuesdays.
I don't know.
What is it?
Takoyaki!
Beef takoyaki!
Look at this!Look at this.
Oh, my God.
Yes, this is a toy cube.
Delicious looking toy cubes!
Here! This is where my family came from!
Here! Main Street.
Does this place look like anything to you?
What's that?
Oh, Yabashi and Kiyoshi.
What?
They want onigiri.
Okay, guys!
You're in for a treat!
Let's go.
I want onigiri.
Yes, please eat onigiri.
I'm hungry.
I'm going to Onigiri-san.
I'll go to the exhibition there, too.
I'm taking the day off.
Why...
Okay, next time.
There's another panel of faces.
I wonder what this is.
I'm not sure.
I don't know what it is, but...
Come on in.
What is this? What is this?
Some kind of god?
What do you want to eat?
I don't know.
Curry and rice.
But it looks so good!
Oh, they have curry and rice.
Do you do curry and rice? Just now.
Oh, it just started?
You want to come in?
Yes, please.
I'm gonna go eat.
Umamiya Restaurant.
What do you think?
I'll have a set meal.
Curry's good, right?
I'm sure it's good curry.
I'll have the Hida beef curry.
I'll have the Hida Beef Curry.
With frankfurters.
What about me?
I want to eat rice.
Miso-yaki sounds good, too.
Looks good!
I wonder what a "houbou" is.
The leaves... the big leaves...
Kashiwa-mochi style?
Oh, yes, yes, yes...
There was a gift shop, right?
Yes, there was. There were a lot of gift shops.
Buy a sarbobo.
I want a Salvovo.
Hey.
Sarvobo.
Salvovo.
but my hands are tied.
Tokai Compliance
I don't think I can sing the parts of people who don't sing
People's parts
They don't look good together.
Yes, the part where he's saying the lines.
They're desperate, you know? Because people can't listen to it.
In 5.
I'm never going to get any of that.
The part of the person. Then I'm in 6.
Do you say "Dai, Goujou, Dai"?
Five...
Did you say "big"?
Five... two every time, sar-bo-bo-bo-tul-say.
Every time 2!
What's the rhythm of the 5 thou?
5 jo...
What was it, two every time?
Five, two every time.5jou every time 2sar bobo tsurusei
6jo first and...
Boom Boom Boom Boom
7Jou car alone
ughhhhhh...
I'm a fan of these places, too, and I want you to do them with me.
I want you all to do this.
I want you to do that at the end.
I mean with your mouth, like this, while you're doing it.
"Uhhhhhh.
Or uh-uh-uh-uh-uh is a police car.
"The Red Mountain Guidebook.
The origin of the "suyake sarubobo".
Why don't monkey gobos have faces? The reason why the monkey gobo doesn't have a face is so that the monkey gobo can see its own feelings through it.
When he is happy, he smiles. When they are sad, they look like they are crying. I was surprised to know that.
Wow, I see. So it's a projection?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I never really paid attention to the fact that they don't have faces.
Indeed.
Wow.
Salvova was born in the Showa period.
He's much older than me.
Idol's very popular language.
Ah, dialect.
Beans?
Are you well?
Oh, here.
Ansama, Ne-sama, Bow and Bee, they all didn't look at me.
Singer Issa.
Singer Issa?
Singer Isa says thank you.
Hey.
Wait, wait. This...
Seriously?
That's definitely not true.
This is terrible. This is really interesting.
There's a ranking of interesting sentences in dialects,
The fourth place is "you" in "wari".
You..."... "Wari...".
Then, skipping the third place, the second place was "nanchara" in hirazu.
And No. 1 was a marble.
It's true that all of them are totally different from each other, isn't it?
Only the third place was concrete in the dialect called concretion.
It's not just a reaction.
Wait, wait, wait. What's wrong with this one?
This is the same thing.
It's a dialect that can be used in everyday life.
The first place goes to "Thank you ena.
Thank you in Thank you ena.
Abaena de bye-bye.
Soyasoya de un-un.
I'm sorry in kowaisa.
I thought it was something a little different.
First place, fifth place.
Please, I'm begging you.
Please, please, please.
You're going to do that?
Next time
Frankfurters!
I'm starving!
This looks pretty hot.
Oh, no!
You see the snow? There you go.
Oh! The texture is different.
This is no ordinary frankfurter.
Mmm!
Delicious.
Ta-da-yang, ta-da-yang, ta-da-yang!
Here you go, Hoba Miso Lunch!
Yes!
Delicious!
Only the meat is turned upside down!
What did I order?
I ordered the Hiragyu Hoba Miso Set Meal!
Looks so delicious!
Wow, it's so good!
Yes, you can have the Houba Misoyaki Set Meal!
Here is a plate of rice!
I'll have another serving of this rice.
Yes, please!
Cheese!Yes, cheese.
Bon appétit.
Oh, it's so sweet.
Yummy!
Delicious.
Well, well, well...
Oh, my gosh!
Amazing! Delicious!
Sweet!
It smells like meat.
It's like fat.
It's great!
Want some? Curry.
Yes, please.
Bon appétit.
Isn't it sweet?
Sweet!
Curry is too good!
Bon appétit.
Where's the miso?
Miso is at the far end.
Bon appétit!
So soft!
Miso is good, right?
Yes!
Thank you!
Thank you for the food!
It was so delicious!
Umami is good!
I'd like to see the souvenirs.
I want to look at the souvenirs for a moment, and then I want to try to mess up the bread!
What bread? Bread comes out of a machine gun?
I don't know.
All I know is that it's there.
Where is the gift shop?
I want a Salvovo on Silver Street.
Oh, there?
Oh, the pumpkin shop?
They have a pumpkin shop.
I'd like to go into the gift shop here.
Is this a good place?
I bought a salvo!
Yay!
I bought some for Yuruki and Haru too, so I'm going to amiage
Well then, let's get on with it
I'm going for the bread!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Oh, that and hiroshige
It's a mess, that's why it's unattended
Yes, it is
Oh, it's on.
It's unmanned and open 24 hours.
Yes, right here.
I'm Mr. Hiroshige.
Hi.
Good morning.
What's this place?
What's going on? What do you mean?
Oh, my God! It's like we're in the bathtub!
It's like we're in the bathtub.
Thank you in advance.
Please make sure there are capsules inside before you put your money in.
If there is no capsule inside, it is sold out.
There's only one capsule.
Oh! Just in time!
Let's see...
They won't let you put money in.
Let me put some money in.
How much should I put in for now?
A thousand yen bill.
May I?
Rumble, rattle, rattle!
Put a 1,000 yen bill in a piece of bread.
Inside the capsule, take out a key with a number on it.
Insert the key into the same box as the key, the numbered box
Both hands in!
I got it!
Here it comes, here it comes!
What's the number?
Whoa!
Whoo!Wow!
They know, and they've flipped it over with Dad.
Yeah!
What's the key?
14!
What?
Fourteen.
Fourteen!
Here!
Now!
Round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round, round.
What?
There's 1,0005 gold in there.
That doesn't mean it's a hit.
What? Bingo!
One two-size and one one-size.
One size fits all?
Isn't that right?
I don't know, but that's a lot!
That's a lot!
Yay!
I'll be right back.
me me me
Mm-mm-mm
mmm